<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CV Builder</string>
    <string name="cvbuilderlogo">CV Builder Logo</string>
    <string name="aboutme">Some text</string>
    <string name="dummy">dummy text</string>
    <string name="careernote">
        <b>Completed </b>on campus studies and currently taking distance education courses to complete a masters\'s degree in computer science ( available for full-time , <b>W-2 </b>employment)\n
    </string>
    <string name="profsummary">Professional Summary</string>
    <string name="about_me">Motivated software developer with more than 6+ years of hands-on, professional experience in the full-stack design and development of software solutions, using all phases of the Software Development Life Cycle. Skills cover a variety of languages and technologies such as Java, Angular 2+, Spring Framework, Oracle PL/SQL. Have MS and BS in Math and Computer science.</string>
    <string name="education">
        <b>Languages:</b> C#, .NET Framework, .NET Core,Java 8, VB.NET,C++ 98/11 STL, Win32 API\n
        <b>Web Development:</b> ReactJS, Vue.JS, NodeJs, ASP.NET MVC, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript, RESTful API, GraphQL.\n
        <b>Databases/ORM:</b> Entity Framework/(LINQ), MS SQL, T-SQL, LLBLGen 2.4 (ORM), Redis, MongoDb\n
        <b>Reports:</b> Crystal Reports, SSRS\n
        <b>Design Patterns/System Design:</b> Strategy, Template, Observer, Composite, Iterator, Command, COR, State, Abstract Factory, CQRS, Domain Driven Design, Microservice Architecture.
        <b>SDLC:</b>  Agile, Waterfall\n
        <b>Testing:</b> xUnit, Basic knowledge of Selenium and Jest.\n
        <b>CI/CD, Version Control:</b> AzureDevOps, Docker, Git Action, Git, TFS\n
        <b>Tools:</b> VS1998-2022, VSCode, Eclipse IDE, Draw.IO, StarUML, Postman, Putty, SSH, FileZilla, Postman.\n
        <b>Platforms:</b> Windows, Linux, macOs\n
    </string>
    <string name="projects">
        <b>Information Retrieval System (2014):</b> Provided searching feature for large-scale text pool including document indexing, searching, and ranking. Technologies Used: Lucene.NET 3.0.3 / C#.NET.\n
        <b>File Parser (2014):</b> Developed file parser for frenetic network programming language. Technologies Used: C++ Language.\n
        <b>Al-Azhar Web Book (2013):</b> Convert Paper-Pack Arabic Learning Material into Digital format on CDs. Technologies Used: VB.NET, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.\n
        <b>School Messaging System (2013):</b> Provided SMS functionality to pre-developed School Management application. Technologies Used: VB.NET.\n
        <b>Goal (2012):</b> Created system to keep track of players actions during match. Technologies Used: VB.NET, Access, Crystal Reports.\n
   <b>Aviation Scheduling CG (2012):</b> Developed system directed to help specific small jets with no center of gravity on board to help crew to distribute passengers. Technologies Used: VB.NET, Access.\n
    </string>
</resources>